<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>planning application on Planning Assistance</title><link>https://planning-assistance.co.uk/tags/planning-application/</link><description>Recent content in planning application on Planning Assistance</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><atom:link href="https://planning-assistance.co.uk/tags/planning-application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comment on a Planning Application</title><link>https://planning-assistance.co.uk/detail/comment-on-a-planning-application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://planning-assistance.co.uk/detail/comment-on-a-planning-application/</guid><description>It is natural to have concerns when a planning application is submitted next door or in your neighbourhood. The planning system is there to reduce any negative impacts of new development, and the legal requirement to consult on applications aims to make sure the views of anyone affected by a development are considered.
However, comments from the general public often end up dismissed as being “non-material considerations”; this means they are not enforceable under planning policy or legislation.</description></item><item><title>Planning Applications</title><link>https://planning-assistance.co.uk/detail/planning-applications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://planning-assistance.co.uk/detail/planning-applications/</guid><description>Planning Assistance provides a full planning manager service to meet the needs of your project.
I can help you submit the following applications:
Full planning permission Householder planning permission Outline planning permission Reserved matters consent Advertisement consent Lawful development certificate Prior approvals Discharge of planning conditions Removal or variation of planning conditions Minor material amendment to a planning permission Non-material amendment to an existing planning permission The planning application management service is adaptable to your requirements and the size of your project.</description></item></channel></rss>